Right.
So this is how seamless it is to
take a course, right?
Um, and artificial intelligence helps you to streamline
the entire process because at the end of
the day, you have the to make things
happen.
Right?
So what do you think about this automation
process?
Because I know that creating courses can be
very, very tiring.
Um, and it's very demanding, but I think
the hardest part of this process right now
is setting up the system.
Um, setting it off for the very first
time may be a bit tricky because you
have to ensure that your AI is properly
set up.
Your LMS is properly connected.
There are just a couple of things that
you need to put together.
But once you're able to pull those things
together, it's easier for you to make some
move and execute whatever you need.